Hello, everyone.
New week. New webinars.
I hope you guys are doing well.
How
is
how's been your weekend?
Did you find some time to
take some rest and,
have fun?
Or everyone is like me just doing crazy hours and
working on this, like,
numerous projects and, you know, trying to
deliver on
time.
With my next iOS,
client pipe,
lined up for me for this week. Super super pumped.
Working started. Yes.
Yeah. Big crowd. Nice.
You guys, do you have do you have any new
people here who just joined very recently? Can you say
new in the chat?
It's for me to understand how many of of you
guys are here.
Yeah. Oh, Mother's Day. Yeah. We had Mother's Day. Yeah.
We did some stuff yesterday. It was fun.
You're right.
Yeah.
New. New. Nice. Welcome.
Yeah. You say hello. Hi, everyone. I got feedback that
these webinars are very early for Europe, but apologies.
I couldn't find different time.
Australia. Nice.
Yeah. So
today's 1 sorry. Before we go there,
before we go there, I see people
some people that I know and already attended this type
of webinars.
Has everyone installed for for those of you who has
the iOS, have you guys
installed
deep
research skill
already, all of you?
I'll be nudging you, like, every every time now.
I see tremendous value from this specific skill, for the
system. And if you're not using it, I want to
invite you on stage and ask why. Sorry. I'm joking.
But,
nope. Not yet.
Yes.
Yeah. I got it.
Yeah.
Those of you who got it,
what's your feedback? How do we find it?
And, again, like, you can extend it. You can expand
it to do, you know,
Jocelyn. Oh, man. You're missing
you're missing the fun.
Look, Michael,
yes. You can go through the workshops.
You can go through the videos and stuff, but, you
know, if you still
if you want speed, yeah, you can just go literally
through the text
version of all of that.
Yeah. Okay. No good feedback.
Okay. Obviously, Marcus said it's amazing, but
that's it. Alright. Anyway
yeah. People, you will love it. You need to do
that. You need to speed things up. The moment you
you need to, like, you know, do like, stop doing
everything and set up AIOS
going through the course. And by the end of it,
you want to install this deep research. That should be
your, you know, number 1 priority. Once you do all
of that, things will get much, much easier in your
life generally. I had the oh my god. That was
like sorry.
Monday is my personal story day in LinkedIn, so I
feel like I can follow the same,
schedule here. So I did the my my sister asked
me my sister's husband is looking for a job, and
he is financial
adviser or some sort of, like, accountant and
adviser. I don't know his role title,
in particular, but, he they came to me and asked,
like, okay. We've got, like, this new,
job. They want us, like, for for this interview, then
they want they want us to do this exercise, this
homework to
do some, like, financial, like like, finance,
finance planning
first and then also
kind of coming up with the answer for the specific,
like, accounting related question about balancing
about balances.
And,
and so, like, the brief is clear. It was, like,
for Dubai, for UAE,
and then,
they got their numbers using their AI. They are just
basic, like, ChargePoint or something. And I've used deep research
combination of deep research,
and my cloud code.
And it went and literally, like, went through, you know,
all the laws, all the changes in accounting,
in taxation, in UAE.
My my sister is, like, based in Belarus, like, have
have never been probably
Dubai before.
And, so we listed all these, so they don't have
any context about what's going on there,
through their network.
And then it listed, like, all these changes historically
before, after, like, everything that needs to be considered for
accounting.
And they, you know, created this proper plan, proper answer
to the to the recruiter with the with, you know,
everything that needs to be said.
And then next day, she's coming back to me and
said, like, holy crap. Like, how can I get access
to that system?
Like, your answer is actually correct 1, and the 1
that we get from our system is wrong. And my
husband just, you know, put time aside and kind of
went through all of that manually. And so we proved
to them that the system is actually very capable.
I just ran it. I I was operator. I have
no clue about accounting at all. I I don't have
that
thing at all for me, no experience. And the system
proved to me yet another time that, you know, any
topic,
any industry you take, you can become
much more knowledgeable, much more skillable.
And all you need to do is, yeah, do what
I said,
AOS plus deep research, and you will love it.
Yes. So this
where's my slide? Sorry. I just had a call that
just finished literally
before right before
this 1. Okay. These are my slides.
I will go and start sharing all of that.
Yeah. Stay bear with me. Sorry. I'll share
share entire screen. I think that should be fine.
Alright.
I think I'm good.
Okay.
Oops.
Not this 1.
Alright.
Okay.
Oops.
Oh, man. This isn't good.
Alright.
Now I'm done.
I'll enable q and a, by the way.
But I usually look into the
chat and look for the questions you have or any,
you know, ideas.
I value these settings sessions as well. But,
as I said,
in the other workshops,
you want to use this, as an opportunity to learn
and also
to
ask questions and discuss or bounce, you know, some ideas
out of all of us here.
And, that's where
that's where the power of community comes in.
And, also, whenever you do something, whenever you achieve something,
don't
don't feel shy to,
actually, you know, message
in the share you build
or in some other channels in the in the community
so you can,
help others to
understand the potential.
Like, sharing your story, sharing your work, sharing your builds
or skills is is super valuable.
So,
for
so last week, what we've been doing last week, we've
been doing a couple of workshops
Thursday and and Friday to go
to do the sort of cloud based
sort of, like, decoupling part of the local local locally
based AIOS
into the shareable
database. So kind of decoupled,
meetings, put it in the server
as a Postgres, as a super base, and then connect
it. So instead of going and doing the
n 8 10 for triggers, I showed how you can
do the same with railway via scripts via Python scripts.
So this
combination of 2, SuperBase and railway for
Python API to capture all the webhooks,
is a good combination.
This week, I've got my 3 last workshops. So today,
I will be going with you through
packaging oh, sorry. Repackaging AOS into single installable
single installable bundle, which might be super useful.
And then
after that,
tomorrow, I think I will be going through
VPS setup. And
Wednesday,
I think I will be going through some of that
compliance
issues,
how you can
encrypt things here, how you can,
you know, do some of these recommendations
from Europe and USA to be more or less compliant
with with this build with this AIOS.
So, yeah, for today, repackaging AIOS. So what I realized
for myself when installing,
AIOS for for my clients is that
so as, like, literally, like, my experience, first very first
client, I go and I literally sit all with them
on the call,
and then I
gave give them
the zip file, like the archive,
and I asked them to do everything, like, via kind
of directing them through the voice. And they can they
they were capable. They're technically capable. So it was not
an not a problem to guide them around the screen
and show them what
to do.
And then, yeah, we succeeded. That was all fine. It
took probably
8, sesh 8 hourly, maybe 7.
No. Probably, we shift everything in probably in 5, but
then we also did probably 2 or 3 sessions to
kind of do these builds together so they can also
learn how to actually build the new skills and everything
and improve their system.
But it was quite,
yeah, quite slow, quite
non effect not effective at all. So from that moment,
I started to think, okay. What's what's, like, what's the
better way to
do it for for your clients? And by the way,
if anyone has experience, you know, doing it for your
clients, feel free to share how you guys are doing
it because, yeah, this experience is super valuable for everyone.
You guys see active in the chat. Nice. I love
it.
Productivity x 100. Yes. Yes, Sergei.
I feel the same. Probably not up to your level,
though. You showed me that,
wireframe. I'm still, like,
you are crashing through that. Like, the system you're building,
like, very complex.
Question. So when you create projects, you
build separate AS for each project.
Yeah. So
so
that that was my my experience. And then after that,
I got this idea to obviously, you improve
your deliverables.
You improve your processes every time you you install it
for the next client. So it should be always, like,
you know, we should always have these,
documents, SOPs,
all the materials
in sort of, like, dynamic modes always
tend to
have markdown file to back up your,
PDFs, your giveaways, your handouts,
such as you can then go and, you know, improve
every time you
go through the next client. And yesterday, I did. So
I had my second client, and I did a skill
to extract
everything
from that installation.
So I would read, you know, all the emails, all
the PDFs I sent, all
the meetings, and I would I created a skill that
extracts, you know, how this specific install went.
So this became my new, like, you know, kind of
next
diff for
for integrating into, like, all the processes that I have
for that. And it it's this this is super helpful.
So and then I have my next client, and I
am kind of now,
like, structure is improving, you know,
constantly.
And then for this 1, this time, I want to
create also,
to
I want to create sort of, like, a single installable
package that you can
have, and that 1 will speed up, you know, your
installation,
of this AIOS. So you don't really need to go
through all of that step by step.
Although
although you
kind of need to follow the same order, but we'll
see where we can go today, where we can what
we can achieve in today's workshop. By the end of
it, I want,
to have a skill that will be able
to actually, I I don't go there because I have
my slides.
Sorry. Host,
it's not important.
And,
what do we cover? Theory,
build,
and then quick q and a. Q and a, yeah,
obviously, you can ask any questions as we go.
The ones that you ask in q and a section,
I always see if you ask them and you talk
a lot, so I might just miss them.
And the build part will
be the most the the the major focus for us
today.
Sorry. I'll just do that. Oops.
Alright.
So
what's the current process rights? Again, like I explained my
process, this was very similar to this.
I had to download every module.
Some of them had been updated. So it was, like,
the first month,
after it all went live. So it was a bit
tricky. So I had to go manually to note all
these,
zips and then
go through them 1 by 1. Right?
Anyway, sorry. Before I call before I continue,
can you guys let me know if you've done any
installation for any of your clients?
Just maybe say a number, like 1 2 5 20,
with the number representing how many of them you've done.
So, again, I have a better understanding of the group
here.
But yeah. So in total, I calculated there are 9
modules, 9 kind of archives
just for the core, just for, you know, 5 layers,
and
it's it's a lot.
And then what I realized, alright. We can probably do
a better job at this.
And then we can improve that process as we go
because, you know,
engineering or, technically, you can create the best, the easiest
installation process on the planet, but
you always want to make it,
work for your your needs, for your cases because everyone
is coming from different background. Right? Everyone has different
technical
capabilities. Someone someone
someone can go and do, you know, docker dockerized deployments.
Some some of you can do VPSs. Some of you
can do MacMini. Some of can some of you can
only go with
Flash stick
to the laptop, connect it, and kind of,
copy and install it from here
from there. So,
that's where, you know, you can't really trust the,
you know, existing,
existing processes that other people give you. You want to
create because this system helps you to be very,
like, you can be creative, but system helps you to
package your idea
into
the set of actions, you know, installables, all of that.
So you literally you like, every 1 of you most
likely will have different process how you see the installation
for for your clients, and you just come up with
the all the skills, all the modules to back it
up. But, I did some research, and,
generally,
that's how,
like, different people use it. Sorry. Different people like, different
kind of tools, different types of
different types of bundling,
the software and packaging it and deploying and sorry. And
installing it to to the clients.
And as we can see here, there are some,
you know, like, some of you probably
don't even know what is TOML, what is YAML,
all of that. But,
you can package it. You know, you can you can
just do skills. You can do the whole folder with
the template.
You
can do binary,
and put it in the Homebrew.
You can do
Helm charts.
I never heard of it, but
but it may be,
again, like another way of doing this thing. Again, like,
this is coming from my deep research usually, these type
of things. And then if I see oh, okay. So
this 1 is interesting.
December. Okay. Date based versioning is better than December. K.
Nice. Good good idea. I kind of
I kind of I can relate to that
and then split
shipped defaults from upgrade to overrides. Alright. So this might
be also, you know, the idea that's okay. Whenever I
want
to have
installable
bundle created from the version of my system
comparing with the 1 that we have in the course.
And maybe
I kinda follow this bottom 1, understand how best to
do that, and kind of dig deep in into that
1.
And then, no, I don't want to go binary for
that. Although,
again, there will be questions for you, like like
like, how do you how do I make sure that
I install it for someone and then that someone don't
take my installables
and go and start installing it for others. Right? So
these type of questions also always, like, in
I hear them a lot during my calls.
Sorry. I've got too many windows.
But, again, like, you want to consider, like, everything that
you want, all your, like, requirements,
in your head first. Maybe use your explore,
commands to do a better spec,
proper spec for for your process.
And then
and then you kind of create this combination of skills,
and maybe scripts to create these bundles for you as
you go. And then,
I guess, we want we all want to do a
better job next time. We do the same thing,
and then improve it basically, like, always like like, do
this always improving,
process for,
whatever we do here.
And this system is super useful to do all of
that.
And then,
yeah, I guess I don't really want to go and
spend much time on these slides because
they're good. I just want to go into action. Maybe
I'll just switch between
them as we go.
But,
I guess, the problem I identified, like, every model has
their own install MD file if you just open up
them and see what's inside. And,
I guess, we want to find the way how we
can
I was just exploring, and I was just trying to
understand, like, the complexity,
what should be the first step, what should be here?
And then
after going through the deep research and
working going through my cloud codes, I ended up with,
the idea, the process where
I can come up literally with 1 file that I
can and 1 script install that file, and then
I can bundle all this module into that file. And
then,
and then I can pretty much, like, follow everything from
a single session,
with quotes,
and going just, like, nonstop
until I finish everything. So that was my idea that
I,
clarified after doing after going through this deep research, after
going through
after going through
thinking and experimenting with it. And then, yeah, at the
end, we've got this install install
SH file that will just literally call. And, like, you
can literally download it to any any
machine and install it for them.
Again, this like, my machine is Mac, so Windows might
be slightly different.
It's probably like there's no scripts. Maybe there are scripts
now.
I don't follow Windows. Sorry.
But if you have Windows specific questions where we have
coaches who can help you with that as well, like,
Garrett is 1 of them. He's using Windows. So he
will be much better,
at guiding you through the Windows specific
issues.
Anyway, enough slides.
Let's go and build something.
So the way we usually go through
the build part here,
sometimes I do, sometimes I don't. I've got,
some of the preps
on this 1.
So in this case,
I think I deleted all that already.
No. I got it. Yeah. I've got some skill skeleton.
So I did some research, and I
yes. Starter kit.
And I wanted to
yeah. My my point my idea was to create the
skill. Right? So this is the end. Yeah. All of
them. So the prerequisites
is,
sorry, these,
files that I downloaded.
I,
I've got all of them here. By the way, I'll
probably
those of you who don't want to do this manually
was a tedious process for me. Oops.
I'll just
So this core
archive has all 9 modules, and you can simply
download it here from the chat.
And this will be much easier for you to getting
started.
You guys ask a couple of questions. Right? Anyway, I'll
read through the chat later probably.
Unless you have a real question to me, feel free
to
copy it in q and a section.
Yeah. So this is, like, all mod these are all
modules inside of this core. I'll just delete it. Actually,
I'll move
it 1 level up.
Yeah. So we've got this core, and then
and then I've got my CR
here. Open a few of them. What is it, skill?
Oops. Not built.
Alright. So we're good to go.
And
I've got some some
version of that skill built already, but,
again, like, I see biggest amount of value for you
here during these workshops to show how I got there.
And
and
and,
you know, if I just share that skill with you,
you take it, you go away,
you learn nothing. Although, you you got some fish. Right?
But here, I am at your service to actually educate
you how to fish. So that's that's why sometimes it
can become a bit technical. Obviously, you always have these
handouts, and you know
that you can just, you know, plug and play sorry.
Like, take them and go away away with them for
those who
who either really struggle or
or don't have time.
But, you know, this is workshop to begin with, first
of all, and that's where we want to, you know,
learn that process together. So, again, like, the way I'm
running that is through my prompting,
and I'm just showing it's most most of these workshops,
they are live.
And I don't have,
you know, step by step process to back up what
I'm doing here usually, but I've got some preps. So
this research summary, again, you can have it as well
in the chat.
Command error.
Got this
quick
shortcut to get me a file.
So this is, literally
the way I see it. I would just
pull it in, this research summary, and I say prompt.
So I want to build a skill using this research
summary,
that will help me to
package all the
modules for AIOS
and ship it as a single bundle and
install
installable
script so installation script.
Let's explore this idea together here and try to build
that skill.
And then I also have the skill skeleton
that I built in results of going through the
research.
No. There is no SkillMD.
There's there's no there are no these things.
Oh, no.
Clout. Clout. What is it? Sorry.
Login.
Let me log in into Cloud. Hope it's
live and working.
Yeah. I wanted to share this queue with you. Right?
Sorry. The skeleton.
Literally, like, these 2 or 3 files, you can
start
with me right now and do pretty much, like, mimic
what I'm doing
if you want,
and you can get your version of that stuff
done by the end of it.
So you want to build a global scale called AOS
handler that reads the 9 core
pom pom from latest AOS,
packages them into single portable tarball
with a manifest and 2 stage installer. Let's
let's
let's you have that 1 artifact to client.
Yeah. That's about it.
Question before we start, build
now versus
rehearse the workshop here because
I don't have that skill.
What are you talking about?
Don't
have the yeah. Okay. No. It's saying that it wants
to put it there.
Alright. We're building it for production today,
right now.
And then if you have time, we can see it
in action.
Skill location. Yeah. I like your idea. Yeah. Let's do
it under skills
ARS
handler in this workspace, please.
Just only in this workspace.
The prebuilt
artifacts.
Yeah. It doesn't exist.
Anything from the skeleton you want to change.
Just double make sure that we save everything in the
outputs folder
in the single folder. Don't create many files,
and sorry. Don't don't put files into the root folder
of this workspace.
Okay.
So we'll see how it goes, and I'll be switching
to the chat to answer some of your questions if
you
have any.
As Jocelyn, do you see it as
a pyramid? No.
Do you see it, like
and, like, again, question 2.
So so Joseline,
posted the the image there.
And,
yeah, this is
very nice diagram
explaining
every
layer.
And from my experience, like, literally, I spend most of
my time with this system doing
mostly build.
Sorry.
As in, like, built and automate. To me, they are
the same.
They are 1 context.
And, again, like, I see this,
Yeah.
Yeah. Anyway, sorry. I was reading through. Oh, wow. It
went.
Yeah, decided to go ahead and actually create this skill
for me, which is super nice of cloud. So probably
we'll go through it faster.
So it went ahead and created this folder, skill.
So what do we do? We package the unite oh,
by the way,
I don't probably need that.
Shipping errors and the client on the fresh machine.
Setting up. Yeah. That's exactly what we wanted, setting up
iOS on a new personal machine. Yeah. You can let's
say you have, another machine,
or you have, an idea for another iOS. Let's say
you have 1 for your business and then another 1
you want to be for your personal or for your
wife or for your partner.
And then,
you pretty much go from there.
You can
speed up this installation as well, producing reproducible
snapshots.
We've got we've got everything there.
Bundle. Nice. It will give us the package,
and every every package will have this manifest YAML. So
the way I see
in the future how you can improve this system is
to literally,
like, I've been building for 4 months. I recognized, okay,
some businesses will benefit from some of these models that
I built, let's say, for lead generation, for outreach, for
content generation. Right? But
not all of them. So maybe I can come up
eventually with, you know, the
the installation that will contain, you know, some of these
modules,
in addition to the base,
to the base 1
to the core 1. And that's how I can use
this approach, this idea for the YAML, for the manifest
YAML to maybe have this,
bundler,
this skill to first
have an interview for me to ask, like, who I'm
installing it
for, and then ask me what are the modules you
want to be brought into
the installer.
So that's that's where you can then, you know, version
number 2, version number 3, where you can,
where you can go from this 1.
I think
it's not quite Oh, wow. We did that already.
I saw it. Sorry.
So I noticed how this starter kit is
is
somewhere at the end
of your manifest
file.
Can
you double check that this actually happens first? Because this
because this starter kit is the very first step we
need to do, not the last 1.
Can you give me an idea? Can you give me
the explanation why this
installation
install order, why you have a iOS starter kit at
the end
at the end, not as the first 1?
So I expected to see
it at the front. Okay. Let me check what actually
inside rather than trust give it an assumption.
So it will probably unpack it and reads through
what is inside.
If you find any issues with this order, please,
update
skill skeleton MD file here
to address these,
findings
or problems.
You're absolutely right. Looking at the actual ZIP, content tells
a different story. So that's the skeleton. Okay. What is
it? Okay. Okay. Okay.
What is this? This is the very first module they
install. Okay. So probably,
when I was doing my research and analysis,
it realized that,
the first model is actually that 1 because it just
says that,
but it didn't pick up that the
the starter kit is actually
the skeleton
Foundation.
So I would do this prompt to update this,
skill skeleton MD file,
and then this is going to be most likely the
1 that I will be attaching to the workshop as
well.
Because there was an issue, and this happens a lot.
This happens all the time.
And the more flexible, the more comfortable you become to,
you know,
go through these problems and challenges yourself, then the faster
you go with your
with your EOS
improvements.
So this 1 is fine. I just want to check
what it did for the actual
bundler templates, install prompts. Alright. So it created install prompts.
Where is that? Bundler templates.
Okay. This guy.
Hard rules never read out.
Your cloud running.
Alright.
Phase a, preflight, manifest
a gates.
That's all fine. Phase b,
Their layer
flow. Create a fresh extract.
Yeah. Oh, wait wait a second. Fire. It's
absent and not layered.
Not not and the layer is not. Yeah. So
yeah. So it kind of emphasized
step 3 that we need to start with that 1.
Then for this 1 first, these layerships, the work workspace
skeleton.
Nice. Nice. All good. I had deal with I'm happy
with all of that now.
Much, much happier. Nice. Alright. So what's the end here?
Again, my practice, my habit is whatever like, if I
if you if I've come up with the
implementation
for something complex, I definitely want to go through the
summary,
and kind of carefully study what has happened,
especially if they deleted any files, if it changed any
files.
Here, we just, yeah, we just updated the template YAML
file, which is also the 1
probably will define the whole process.
No. This 1 is simple. Right? But the idea behind
this, repackaging
will probably be
it's kind of it's kind of become a matter of
how
complex your manifest,
template I'm sorry. Manifest YAML file becomes,
eventually as you grow. And then, literally, you can have,
you know, you can have
core
just like this. Then you can do extra modules. Let's
say you go and do this deep,
research 1, and it has 6 modules,
to do first
before you go to the final 1. Right? So the
final 1 is just a prompt,
with,
kind of, like, packaging sorry, grouping, like the previous 5
or 6 of them under the same umbrella.
And then you can add more stuff. You can maybe,
you know, automate creation
of some of these,
like, inter OS layers
that or so inter OS,
collectors there. And you can, you know, improve your manifest
such as then it knows exactly what you want to
install for that next client.
There was something else I forgot, but I'll remember about
it later.
Alright. So maybe we just do a quick test of
what's of the skill now.
And then sometimes I'm like
I'm like, why these are in red?
Why some of these files are in red? Can you
give me explanation?
And I just go and ask questions.
That's
again, this is for demo, so you are not scared
with everything that is happening on your
screen. And, you know, the the quicker you understand that,
the faster you go again.
This folder contains
untracked files.
Once you get ads and commits,
and it should turn into gray as normal. Okay. Let's
do commit.
But then
how do we demo?
Can you
create a set of
instruct set of commands for me to run-in my terminal
to
create a fresh
installation for another client.
If I can't even sell free AI to my own
family, I'm doomed.
Look. I think,
there are reasons for that.
So don't,
you know, don't go hard on yourself.
The first priority needs to be you know, you need
to understand the potential for yourself first, and then you
need to prove
yourself that you're
getting value and you're getting,
you know, your, like, your your tasks done, your goals
done with with that system.
It's literally,
let's say, you're talking to everyone about how good it
is and how you can earn more money with it,
but your
balance sheet stays flat. And, obviously, something is
out of sync. If you
want to sell it to others
for that
specific at that angle, like, you can earn more than
you need to show them. Okay. This is my earnings
going up month by month. If you
are doing your content generation, for example, with this system,
you want to show them
look. I've
I had that's, you know, I had that's,
graph before I started, and this is my new graph
with my, I don't know, number of posts, impressions, whatever
you name it. And then you
but you need to prove it to yourself first. Right?
So you need to achieve all of that, and then
it will be really easy talk.
Took me a year to kind of,
like, yesterday with my wife, we had the conversation that
now she wants to to use the iOS as well.
So
so, yeah, I I hear you. It's it's not easy.
But,
but she wanted to actually when she the the moment
she realized, you know, the power of that even, like,
deep research skills, she immediately came back to me. She's
like, can I have it? Can I have it? Can
I have it?
So now she can,
do, you know, any research about, you know, her agenda,
about her needs
much much faster, much easier.
Sales agent. Nice.
Do you mind sharing any details behind that agent that
you did?
Itavi?
Alright.
I'll just do that.
1 time at the bundle.
Alright.
Okay. Code code is installed.
Some prerequisites
prerequisites.
So, again, like, I shared the files. If you're on
Windows, you best if the best option for you to
create such a skill is to go through,
probably, like, when you install this skill that I will
share, like, ASB handler, it should capture all of that.
But, again, like, if something doesn't work best, if you
just
go through through that same process and create that skill
yourself using your Windows
system. Alright. So,
yeah, let's just,
what is it? I'll just open.
Just probably open,
pull them by oh,
damn.
Open them side by side,
and then
try to do that.
So the
place here
place.
We didn't run the bundle. Sorry.
I just realized we we didn't create anything yet.
Probably I need to open new
session.
And we actually need to do a iOS bundle,
and then let's provide the source.
Yeah. So that's what we build. I can say now,
okay. This is my this is my source, and I
just go like that
and see what
happens.
That was quick.
So it yeah. It created
outputs folder, and it
created today's 1, and these are 3 files. Alright. That's
good.
Now can you
can you create,
can you show me the commands I need to use
to install this bundle that I just created
in the terminal for myself here.
So I will be yeah. Just just just use all
the
commands
that I need. I don't want to copy any I
don't want to do anything manually. Just give me all
the commands here first.
Extract the bundle
to a staging dir. Okay. Let's create this staging dir.
And then
to that 1.
then we copy
we copy no. We run install.
And so we we unpacked
the the star file into this temporary folder, and then
now we run this install. Sh from that folder.
So it said,
AIS bundle staged
here now as a test. Yeah. That's how we want
it. Next step, stage 2. Cloud code drives
the layer by layer install, CD there, close it close
the dot and paste the content of install prompt into
the chat.
Where is that install prompt? Yeah. It's inside of the
folder. Right. So it should be all there. So we
just do CD. Oops.
Just go to that folder and do cloud
cloud dot.
Yes. Trust this folder.
Nothing there.
Right. Okay. Which is fine.
So we just go to that same folder,
CD,
and then we do cursor. If using Versus code, you
just need to type code
dot,
cursor space dot, and it will open
that folder in the cursor for you immediately,
or Versus code.
Alright. So we only have this guy here. Right? So
just the files
and manifest YAML.
And then just copy this,
prompt.
Oops.
Oops. And paste it here.
Your cloud code running inside a freshly staged AIS target
directory. The operator has just pasted this prompt into chat.
The current working directory containing 9 core files
manifest.
Never read out. Try to yeah. So just follow the
instructions.
Just what do we want.
Alright.
While it's thinking and going through that, so check the
questions.
To clarify, did you say that for those on Windows,
the best person to speak to re
iOS setup is Garrett?
Yes.
That's what I said. He he has Windows. He is
using this AIOS setup.
He's running his AIOS on Windows.
So it will be much easier,
to speak about any challenges.
If the challenges are,
like, operating system specific,
all the concepts, all the kind of how do I
build this and that can go to any dev coach,
to be honest.
All of us know how to use the system.
We all have it, and then
you can book call with any of us.
I love I love this on 1 level. The packaging
is something we should be doing that we didn't know
we needed.
On the other hand, this is reproducing what software engineers
have had as tools like
Ansible and puppets
that can build these scripts for you for decades.
Yes. Exactly. Well, you can go wild again. You can,
so my system is slightly different.
Kind of I I did couple of improvements.
Oh, good example will be that
productivity OS that we productivity layer that we improved in
1 of the workshops
that now knows about your priority. It can send you
daily briefs with your tasks. It can prioritize,
you know, just take the first, you know, 5 of
them and and show it there.
I've taken the advice from or idea that someone posted.
And, actually, for my build, I created the
section to do
this step that will also book,
1 task for my calendar.
Knowing my calendar, I just placed that, you know, 1
hour block to do 1 important task for a day
to keep me concentrated and disciplined.
So that would be where,
you can then okay. You've got this base, but you
also have your, you know, changes. And then you can
come up with the process that will, you know, instead
of going with the base 1 we provide, you can
go and, you know, create this, bundle for for the
version that you have if you think that yours is
better.
Alright. Phase a preflight summary bundle.
Get in front. Preflight. Okay. Type go. Okay. We we
say go.
And some of you guys are missing these slash commands,
for whatever reason. These are this is the package that
has,
explore and brain and brainstorm. These are 2 very important
commands.
So don't forget to install these ones as well if
you just, you know, if you're just new and you're
going through,
through the installation yourself
manually.
Garrett's
well, there's only 1 Garrett.
If you go to
oh, not this guy.
Sorry. Book a call.
If you go to the,
book a call section of the AAA,
Garrett is this guy, Garrett Davis.
Alright. So it did something. I want to check. Alright.
So it unpacked everything. Nice. So it's all fresh and
ready to go.
Is everything here
and all this? So probably 1
improvement can we we can do is to
also, in addition to the changes we did to the
skill skeleton, can you also instruct
the skill to move
the installable
zip files,
to a module installs once
once you unpacked it once you finish the once you
finish the entire installation?
We don't need to do it right at the beginning.
We need to do it at the end of the
installation.
K. And then
what's
next?
Layer 1 of 9. AI starter kit install layer 2
of 9 context. Okay. Now
it
it's
still 1 conversation. It's a long conversation process. Please enter.
Please
press enter to install.
You can press enter. Go.
So and now it will literally, like, from that 1
single session or context session with your code code will
go and
go step by step model by module in the order
we defined
so you don't miss anything.
Go and follow that installation process. So now you just
can see it. Don't do anything. You just go through
the the actual installation.
And
that's pretty much was my goal for today.
So I will package that skill.
Probably, we'll recreate it with the few changes that we
did.
And
after that,
I attached it to this workshop,
and, like, the other 2 or 3
2 files for the research and for the skill skeleton.
So let's say you want to do it yourself,
and follow the, I guess, the
the instructions that I've been giving during this workshop.
But for today's 1, I think we are done. If
you we still have time for a couple of questions
if you if you want.
The
future
of this process, the way I see it, you can,
you know, take take that type of skill. You can
improve it to go
and maybe
maybe even extract the
the interview parts. Right? So there are a couple of
modules where we ask, you know, what you want to
do,
what are your goals. Let's say this context 1 is
interview heavy.
Then a few others, let's say,
when you are up to, you know, your
task audit, There's also a bunch of questions what you
do on daily basis to understand
the potential for these, you know, automations with your current
routines.
And all of that can be extracted potentially
as the interview block.
And then
you can go through that, let's say, with your clients
separately to this installation.
And then at the end of that part, you
just extract all the contacts from them. And that's what
you need. And then you have, you know, combination of
markdown files.
You take them. You come here. You do this installation.
You just upload these documents,
and the system knows everything it needs to know.
And then,
it will literally go through
everything for you,
in 1 go,
without any interruptions.
Then the second part, actually,
you immediately will be thinking about how you actually connect
all the systems. Right? So you need it's obviously part
of that first initial interview could be
asking, you know, asking them about the systems that they
they have to use they are using daily, for example.
But that should be that, like, the,
like, the naming, the the actual list, the set of
the list of platforms should be discovered during that initial
interview with them.
And then
the credentials, the authorization
part,
is a bit trickier because you need them to be
around and provide you with all of them, with all
of this case, with all of the passwords.
The best way, the secured way is if you use
the software to share passwords between between each of you.
But then sometimes they need some,
baby holding to actually go and, you know,
find these places where they need to create and establish
create these API keys.
So you might need an interview for that specific interview
for that specific session, like, online session,
with them to, you know, collect all of that. But
once you went through the interview, you can have a
plan for yourself. Okay.
This is the client. This is their their contacts. This
is what they're using. These are their tools.
And then the plan will be okay. Now you like,
for all of these tools, you need to get the
APIs API keys for them. And you can also come
up with instructions for yourself, such as you go on
the call with them, and then you go through these
instructions, and you literally guide them through the screen what
needs to be done. Or even you can send it
to them,
as the, you know, as the handout, as the homework,
and they come back to you with
with all these API keys if they are kind of
technical and understand how to find these API keys in
the platforms.
So that's that's the future the the the way the
the way I see how you can improve your installation
process. But
I
would be
I'd probably stay,
and read through the chat. You've been very productive here
and see what I missed,
after the after we end here.
And
and, yeah, if you have any feedback on these workshops
workshops, we don't stop them. So we just finish the
daily ones, but then there will be weekly ones after
that. So there will be a lot of topics we
still want to cover in the future. So any feedback
about these ones, future ones,
ideas you want to cover, because we read them. You
you you posted quite a lot of them
in the in the
in different places, actually. Right? So,
that's what we
are after. We want to help you to go faster
with your journey and be more
effective.
But
for today, I think we're done,
unless
you have questions
that I can answer.
Alright. Have a nice day, everyone.
Enjoy your week, and see you around
again, like, tomorrow.
And day after tomorrow, I'll be I'll be doing another
of
these and check the topics there.
Take care. Bye, everyone.